Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series F: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: Miscellaneous and Photographs, / Date(s): 1940-2001 (inclusive) -- 1940-1963 (bulk); F000; / Quantity: 3 boxes; 1 oversize folder / Dimensions: 4 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries FC: GSD Posters, / Date(s): 1990-2001; Folder: FC019; / Quantity: 70 items / Dimensions: varies / Medium: print / Support: paper
Press releases / Press releases BC094
Primitive art / Photographs FB027, FB046
Privileges (permissions) / Memorandums EA051
Prizes / Brochures CC125, FA037
Prizes / Clippings BA024, FA031
Prizes / Contact sheets DC040
Prizes / Newsletters BC032, BC034, FA010, FA036
Prizes / Posters CC136
Procedures / Booklets AB008, AB009, AB010, AB011, AB014
Procedures / Bulletins AB005
Procedures / Cards (information artifacts) AB001
Procedures / Typescripts AA032
Professors / Histories BB001
Professors / Newsletters BC044
Professors / Publications BB038
Programs (documents) / Programs (documents) DB100
Programs (documents) / Publications CB008
Proofs (printed matter) / Typescripts DC031
Protests / Newsletters BC078
Publications / Articles BA020, BA023
Publications / Brochures CB001
Publications / Correspondence BC092
Publications / Invitation cards EA100
Publications / Lists (document genres) BB040
Publications / Notebooks EA099
Publications / Photostats CB014, CB015, CB016, CB017, CB018, CB019, CB020, CB021, DC047, DC052, DC054
Publications / Publications CC022
Publications / Typescripts CC076, CC077, CC078, CC079
Publishers / Articles BA013
Publishing / Correspondence DB057
Real estate / Articles BA012
Real estate / Directories CC131
Receptions / Brochures DB015
Receptions (events) / Brochures DB015
Receptions (events) / Invitation cards EA109
Receptions (events) / Newsletters BC044
Receptions (events) / Notebooks EA099
Receptions (events) / Photographs DB008, FB003
Record covers / Typescripts AA048
Recreation / Flyers (printed matter) FA067
Reference sources / Reference sources FA068, FA069, FA070
Regional planning / Publications EA071, EA095
Registration / Cards (information artifacts) AB001
Releases (permissions) / Forms (documents) BC091
Reminiscences / Newsletters BC030
Reminiscences / Typescripts DC032
Renovations / Photographs EA133
Renovations / Press releases DA004
Research (function) / Booklets DB003
Research (function) / Memorandums BC007, EA051
Research (function) / Reports DB001
Restaurants / Photostats FB024
Restoration (process) / Brochures EA101
Resumes / Resumes AA030
Reunions (meetings) / Agendas (administrative records) DB004
Reunions (meetings) / Booklets BC128, BC129, BC130, BC133, BC135, BC136, BC137, BC138, BC141, BC142, BC143, BC146, BC147, BC148, BC149, BC150
Reunions (meetings) / Brochures BC155
Reunions (meetings) / Folders (containers) BC131, BC134, BC140, BC144
Reunions (meetings) / Lists (document genres) BC151
Reunions (meetings) / Newsletters CA010
Reunions (meetings) / Xerographic copies BC132
Safety glass / Schedules (architectural records) EA022
Schedules (architectural records) / Schedules (architectural records) EA022
Schedules (time plans) / Calendars DC001, DC002, DC003
Schedules (time plans) / Photographs DC028
Schedules (time plans) / Schedules (time plans) AA029
Scholarships / Articles BA015
Scholarships / Newsletters BC050
Schools (buildings) / Lantern slides CC003
Schools (buildings) / Photographs DA013
Schools (buildings) / Reprints BD015
Schools (institutions) / Brochures AA025
Schools (institutions) / Reports AA026, AA027
Sculpture (visual work) / Correspondence EA021
Sculpture (visual works) / Photographs CC049, FB047
Sections (drawings) / Photographs DA009
Security / Reports FA026
Seminars / Booklets CB005
Seminars / Folders (containers) DB041
Sgraffito (technique) / Photographs FB044
Shovels / Correspondence EB011
Shovels / Photographs EB004, EB009
Signage / Memorandums EA028
Signatures (names) / Notebooks EA099
Simulation methods / Reports EB012
Single-family houses / Publications CC023
Site plans / Site plans CC087
Sketches / Xerographic copies CC098, CC100
Societies / Memorandums FA009
Software / Booklets DB003
Solar energy / Newsletters CA006
Space utilization / Typescripts EA007
Special collections / Articles EA153
Special collections / Brochures EA035, EA036, FA065
Special collections / Correspondence EA137
Special collections / Covers (gathered matter components) EA037
Special collections / Lists (document genres) EA018
Special collections / Loose-leaf binders EA139
Special collections / Photographs EA120
Speeches / Typescripts DA014
Stabile / Photographs CC045, CC046, CC047
Stacks (shelves) / Memorandums EA017
Stairs / Photographs EA122
Stationery / Stationery EA079
Statistics / Brochures EA104
Statistics / Data EA003
Statistics / Memorandums BC005
Statistics / Statistics EA060
Storefronts / Articles AA044
Stores / Articles AA044
Strikes (events) / Agendas (administrative records) DB004
Strikes (events) / Documents DB005, DB006
Strikes (events) / Press releases DB002
Strikes (events) / Reports DB001
Structures (structural elements) / Newsletters BC029
Student aid / Booklets AB006, AB008, BB024
Student aid / Brochures BB022, BB023, BB034, EA083
Student aid / Cards (information artifacts) AB001
Student aid / Correspondence BB015
Student aid / Interviews CA008
Student projects / Journals (periodicals) AB004
Students / Annual reports AA015
Students / Booklets AB006, AB007, AB008, AB009, AB010, AB011, FA071, FA072, FA073
Students / Copies CC147
Students / Directories AB003, AB012
Students / Facebooks AB025, AB026, AB027, AB028, AB029
Students / Group portraits EA105, FB001, FB021
Students / Handbooks AB021, AB022, AB023
Students / Leaflets (printed works) FA023, FA024
Students / Lists (document genres) BC059
Students / Memorandums BC005
Students / Newsletters BC078
Students / Photographs DB008, DB009, DB013, EB013, FB050, FB093, FB094
Students / Press releases DB002
Students / Programs (documents) CB004
Students / Registers AB016
Students / Slides DB014
Students / Surveys (documents) AA067
Students / Typescripts DC031
Student work / CD-ROM CB011
Student work / Correspondence CC032, EA152
Student work / Forms (documents) EA140, EA141, EA142, EA143, EA144, EA145, EA146, EA147, EA148, EA149, EA150, EA151
Student work / Notes CC028, CC033
Student work / Photographs CA016, CA020, CA021, CA022, CA023, CA024, FB002, FB015
Student work / Photostats FB023, FB024
Student work / Photostats (copies) FB051
Student work / Press releases CA017
Student work / Typescripts CC093
Studios (organizations) / Newsletters CA014, CA015
Studios (organizations) / Surveys (documents) AA067
Studios (work spaces) / Photographs FB093
Studios (work spaces) / Transparencies FB095
Surveys (documents) / Correspondence EA137
Symposia / Articles BA012
Symposia / Brochures BB021, DB089, DB124, FA007, FA016, FA057
Symposia / Clippings DB056
Symposia / Correspondence DB088
Symposia / Posters BC126, BC127, CC118, CC119, CC120, CC121, FA035, FA039, FC012
Symposia / Press releases DC008
Symposia / Programs (documents) DB103, DB113, FA013
Tables / Memorandums EA025
Tapestries / Clippings BD006
Tapestries / Newsletters CA006
Task forces / Photographs DB034
Taxes / Memorandums BC008
Telephone directories / Telephone directories AA002, AA004, AA005, AB013
Telephones / Memorandums EA028
Text types / Photographs BC017
Theses / Brochures FA056
Theses / Newsletters CA015
Tours (journeys) / Brochures CC153
Townships / Photographs FB002
Traveling exhibitions / Booklets CC135
Traveling exhibitions / Posters CC136
Trusses (structural elements) / Photographs FB085
T-shirts / T-shirts DC039, EB022
Tuition / Cards (information artifacts) AB001
Typefaces (type forms) / Photographs BC017
Typefaces (type forms) / Proofs (printed matter) BC089
Typefaces (type forms) / Samples BC084
Typefaces (type forms) / Specifications BC085
Typography / Contour drawings (drawings) CC081
Typology / Newsletters CA013
Universities (institutions) / Clippings AA011, DB107
Universities (institutions) / Correspondence FA004
Universities (institutions) / Gazettes DB128
Universities (institutions) / Magazines (periodicals) DB111, DB133, DB134
Universities (institutions) / Writings (document genre) BB016
Urban design / Academic prospectuses AA010
Urban design / Bibliographies DB024, FA043
Urban design / Brochures CC133, DB018, DB019, DB021, DB023, DC022, DC023
Urban design / Clippings DB042, DB046, FA031, FB026
Urban design / Contact sheets DC040
Urban design / Correspondence BA002, DB017
Urban design / Interviews CA008
Urban design / Journals (periodicals) DB044
Urban design / Lists (document genres) CC029
Urban design / Newsletters BC037, BC073, CA004, CA014
Urban design / Photographs CC056, FB025
Urban design / Photostats (copies) FB051
Urban design / Press releases DB020, DB043
Urban design / Proceedings DB040
Urban design / Publications DB025, DB038
Urban development / Press releases DC007
Urbanization / Reports EB012
Urban planners / Publications AA066
Urban planning / Academic prospectuses AA010
Urban planning / Brochures DC023
Urban planning / Contact sheets DC011
Urban planning / Publications AA066
Urban renewal / Articles BA012, BA016
Urban renewal / Interviews CA008
Vertical files / Lists (document genres) EA019
Visual arts / Academic prospectuses AA010
Visual arts / Brochures FA066
Vocational guidance / Booklets CB006
Vocational guidance / Newsletters FA010
Volunteers / Lists (document genres) BA004
Walk-ups / Photographs FB002
Wasserman, Joseph / Newsletters CA004
Wastelands / Clippings FA059
Waterfronts / Lists (document genres) BA006
Women / Announcements BC067
Women / Newsletters BC062
Women / Portraits FB030
Women / VHS video DC042
Workshops (seminars) / Memorandums BC006
Workshops (work spaces) / Newsletters BC029
Works of art / Programs (documents) FA001